fontbundles.net 2017-09-02

# Privacy Policy | Font Bundles

Last Updated: 23rd July 2017

Data Protection Licence Number: ZA198379

As the operators of the website https://fontbundles.net/ and https://designbundles.net/ ("Website"), Font Bundles Ltd is committed to protecting and respecting your privacy. This privacy policy ("Privacy Policy") (together with our website terms of use and any other documents referred to therein) sets out the basis on which the personal data collected from you, or that you provide to us will be processed by us. Please read the following terms carefully to understand our views and practices regarding your personal data and how we will treat it.

For the purpose of the Data Protection Act 1998 ("Act"), the Data Controller is Font Bundles Ltd. 

**INFORMATION WE MAY COLLECT FROM YOU**

We may collect and process the following information from you: 

  * Information that you provide by filling in forms on the Website. This may include information provided at the time of placing an order, registering to use the Website (if applicable) or requesting further information or services. We may also ask you for information when you report a problem with the Website.
  * Specifically, personal details such as name, email address, postal address, phone number, financial and credit card information or any information inputted by you when using the Website.
  * If you contact us, we may keep a record of that correspondence.
  * We may also ask you to complete surveys that we use for research purposes, although you do not have to respond to them.
  * Details of transactions you carry out through the Website and of the fulfilment of your orders.
  * Details of your visits to the Website including, but not limited to login information, browser type and version, traffic data, location data, weblogs and other communication data and the resources that you access.

**RETENTION OF YOUR PERSONAL DATA**

We take appropriate measures to ensure that any personal data are kept secure and are kept for the duration of your use of our service. 

If your personal details change or you have any questions about how we use data collected which relates to you, please contact us using the contact details provided below.

We will endeavour to update your personal data within seven (7) working days of any new or updated personal data being provided to us, in order to ensure that the personal data we hold about you is as accurate and up to date as possible.

Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Although we will do our best to protect your personal data, which includes using certain security software, we cannot guarantee the security of your data transmitted to the Website; any transmission is at your own risk. Once we have received your information, we will use strict procedures and security features to try to prevent unauthorised access.

**USES MADE OF YOUR INFORMATION**

We use information held about you in the following ways: 

  * To provide you with our services. 
  * To ensure that content on the Website is presented in the most effective manner for you and for the device(s) you use to access and view the Website. 
  * To provide you with information, products or services that you request from us or which we feel may interest you. 
  * To carry out our obligations arising from any contracts entered into between you and us, this may include sharing your details with third party. 
  * To send you service, support and administrative messages, reminders, technical notices, updates, security alerts, and information requested by you. 
  * To operate, protect, improve and optimise the Website, our business, and our users' experience, such as to perform analytics, conduct research, personalise or otherwise customise your experience, and for advertising and marketing. 
  * To administer our site and for internal operations, including troubleshooting, data analysis, testing, research, statistical and survey purposes. 
  * To notify you about changes to our service. 

In addition to the above uses we may use your information, or permit selected third parties to use your information, to notify you about goods or services which may be of interest to you. For such uses we will only contact you by electronic means (e-mail or SMS) if you have consented to such communication when we collect your data, or if the contact by us relates to goods or services similar to those which were the subject of a previous transaction between you and us.

If you do not want us to use your data in this way, please tick the relevant box situated on the form on which we collect your data.

Where we have asked for permission, but you do not want us to pass your details on to third parties for marketing purposes, do not tick the relevant box on the form on which we collect your data. 

If at any time you no longer wish to receive communications from us, please contact us at sales@fontbundles.net or select the opt-out option in our emails. 

**DISCLOSURE OF YOUR INFORMATION**

You agree that we have the right to share your personal information with: 

  * Any member of our group, which means our subsidiaries, our ultimate holding company and its subsidiaries, as defined in section 1159 of the UK Companies Act 2006. 
  * Selected third parties including, but not limited to: 
    * business partners, suppliers, affiliates, service providers and sub-contractors for the performance of any contract we enter into with them or you; 
    * third party companies or individuals to assist us with fraud prevention and risk assessment, to assist us with customer service, and to facilitate the payments or reimbursements you request; 
    * advertisers and advertising networks that require the data to select and serve relevant adverts to you and others; and 
    * analytics and search engine providers that assist us in the improvement and optimisation of our site. 
  * We will disclose your personal information to third parties: 
    * In the event that we sell or buy any business or assets, in which case we will disclose your personal data to the prospective seller or buyer of such business or assets. 
    * If Font Bundles Ltd or substantially all of its assets are acquired by a third party, in which case personal data held by it about its customers will be one of the transferred assets. 
    * If we are under a duty to disclose or share your personal data in order to comply with any legal obligation, or in order to enforce or apply our website terms and conditions or any other documents referred to therein, 

**IP ADDRESSES AND COOKIES**

We may collect information about your mobile phone, computer or other device from which you access the Website including where available your IP address, operating system and browser type, for systems administration and to report aggregate information to our advertisers. This is statistical data about our users’ browsing actions and patterns, and does not identify any individual. We may, however, use such information in conjunction with the data we have about you in order to track your usage of our services. 

Read more about the individual cookies we use and how to recognise them in our [Cookies Policy](https://fontbundles.net/cookiepolicy). 

**WHERE WE STORE YOUR PERSONAL DATA**

The data that we collect from you may be transferred to, and stored at, a destination outside the European economic area ("EEA"). It may also be processed by staff operating outside the EEA who work for us or for one of our suppliers. Such staff may be engaged in, among other things, the fulfilment of your orders, the processing of your payment details and the provision of support services. By submitting your personal data, you agree to this transfer, storing or processing. We will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this Privacy Policy. 

All information you provide to us is stored on our secure servers. Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password which enables you to access certain parts of the Website, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. We ask you not to share a password with anyone. 

**YOUR RIGHTS**

You have the right to ask us not to process your personal data for marketing purposes. We will usually inform you (before collecting your data) if we intend to use your data for such purposes or if we intend to disclose your information to any third party for such purposes. You can exercise your right to prevent such processing by checking/ticking certain tick boxes on the forms we use to collect your data. You can also exercise this right at any time by contacting us using our contact details set out below. 

The Act gives you the right to access information held about you. Your right of access can be exercised in accordance with the Act. Any access request may be subject to a £10 fee to meet our costs in providing you with details of the information we hold about you. 

The Website may, from time to time, contain links to and from the websites of our partner networks, advertisers and affiliates. If you follow a link to any of these websites, please note that these websites have their own privacy policies and terms of use and that we do not accept any responsibility or liability for these policies and terms of use. Please check these policies before you submit any personal data to these websites. 

**CHANGES TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY**

We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time. Any changes we make to our Privacy Policy in the future will be posted on this page and, where appropriate, notified to you by e-mail or when you login to the website. Please check back frequently to see any updates or changes to our Privacy Policy. 

**CONTACT**

All questions, comments and requests regarding this Privacy Policy should be addressed to sales@fontbundles.net. You may also write to us at Font Bundles Ltd, Office 7, 35-37 Ludgate Hill, London, EC4M 7JN, United Kingdom.
